[
{
   "id":1,
   "questionText":"1. Question: What tag is used to create a hyperlink in HTML?",
   "options":["<link>","<a>","<url>",
    "<hyperlink>]"],
   "ans":"<a>"
},
{
   "id":2,
   "questionText":"2. Question: Which of the following tags is used to define an unordered list in HTML?",
   "options":[ "<ol>","<list>","<ul>","<li>]"],
   "ans":"<ul>"
},
{
   "id":3,
   "questionText":"3. Question: What is the correct HTML tag for inserting a line break?",
   "options":["<br>","<lb>",
   "<break>" ,"<newline>" ],
   "ans":"<br>" 
},
{
   "id":4,
   "questionText":"4. Question: Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?",
   "options":[ "alt",
   "title",
   "src",
   "caption"],
   "ans":"alt"
},
{
   "id":5,
   "questionText":"5. Which HTML tag is used to define the header for a document or section?",
   "options":["<header>","<head>","<title>",
   "<h1>"],
   "ans":"<h1>"
},
{
   "id":6,
   "questionText":"6. In HTML, which attribute is used to specify an inline style for an element?",
   "options":["class","style","id","inline"],
   "ans":"style"

   
},
{
   "id":7,
   "questionText":"7. Which HTML tag is used to define a table row?",
   "options":["<row>","<tr>","<td>","<th>"],
   "ans":"<tr>"
},
{
   "id":8,
   "questionText":"8. What does HTML stand for?",
   "options":["Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language","Hyper Text Markup Language",
   "Home Tool Markup Language",
   "Hyper Transfer Markup Language"],
   "ans":"Hyper Text Markup Language"
},
{
   "id":9,
   "questionText":"9. Which of the following tags is used to create a numbered list in HTML?",
   "options":["<ol>","<ul>","<li>","<list>"],
   "ans":"<ol>"
},
{
   "id":10,
   "questionText":"10. In HTML, which tag is used to define a paragraph?",
   "options":["<p>","<para>","<pg>","<paragraph>"],
   "ans":" <p>"
}



]